Inventory of the Addition to the Papers of Hardy Cross Dillard 1935-1969
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
Addition to the Papers of Hardy Cross Dillard 1935-1969
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
MSS 84-8h
This addition to the Papers of Hardy Cross Dillard consists of 3 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This addition was found in the Law School in the spring of 1995.
Scope and Content Information
This addition to the Papers of Hardy Cross Dillard consists of miscellaneous materials found in the Law School in the spring of 1995. Of particular note are small notebooks and journals kept by Dillard before and during World War II, as well as notes and documents for McClanahan v. California Spray-Chemical Corporation, a case in which Dillard represented the plaintiff before the Virginia Supreme Court.
Contents List
- Almond v. Day. Supplemental Memorandum of Respondent. Opinion by Justice John W. Eggleston 1955 (Box 91)
- Appointment Calendars 1962-1968 (Box 91)
- Case Notes 1952 (Box 91)
- McClanahan Case 1952, 3 folders (Box 91)
- McClanaha Case Drafts n.d. (Box 91)
- McClanahan Drafts-Briefs 1952 (Box 92)
- McClanahan Miscellaneous References 1952 (Box 92)
- McClanahan Outline of Argument [1952] (Box 92)
- McClanahan [Petition of Writ of Error] [1952] (Box 92)
- McClanahan Record n.d. (Box 92)
- McClanahan Record-Design-Analysis-Opinion [1952] (Box 92)
- McClanahan [Reply Brief for Petitioners] [1952] (Box 92)
- McClanahan Trial Court Briefs [1952] (Box 92)
- Miscellaneous Materials n.d. (Box 92)
- Miscellaneous Cases. Notes n.d. (Box 93)
- Newspaper Clippings 1942-1969, 2 folders (Box 93)
- The New York Times 1964 (Box 93)
  Joke
- The University of Virginia News Letter, Vol. xxviii, No. 17 1952 (Box 93)
- Five Small Note Books (Box 93)
  Two of the note books contain notes for teaching and three contain notes made during the war and HCD's trip to China
- Bound Note Book (Box 93)
  Contains reading notes and personal journal,1935-1936